Mihail Deryugin

CONTACT

Mitischi, Moscow region

E-mail: snarksliveshere@gmail.com

Website: http://snarksliveshere.xyz/contacts

COMPUTER SKILLS

Web developer with experience in PHP, HTML5, Git, Css/Css3, SCSS, Gulp, Compass, JavaScript, JQuery, Vue(a little), Laravel (more than Vue, less than MODX, unfortunately), Blade, PhpStorm, composer, npm, bootstrap3, bootstrap4. Experience in Content Management System such as MODX, Wordpress, Bitrix(include bitrix only for list). Strong on MODX, i create about 25 sites and several modules on this CMS.

OBJECTIVE

Motivated PHP Developer seeks employment as part of a dynamic software development

WORK **EXPERIENCE** Ard media

Feb 2017 — Present

PHP Developer

- Develop and maintain e-commerce and other responsive websites using xPDO, MODX, PHP, MySQL, JQuery/JavaScript.
- Created new websites for individuals and business using HTML/HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Gulp and Photoshop.
- Updated and maintained exististing responsive websites to raise CTR.

freelance

March 2010 — Feb 2017

HTML/CSS Developer

• Created and maintained standart based websites using HTML/CSS, jquery, php, mysql, Joomla, Wordpress

Intercom

dec 2008 — feb 2009

Technical support

Technical support in ISP company

QUALIFICATIONS Develop and maintain sites:

- http://www.germes-gp.ru/ (+ developing compare module)
- http://alvita-a.ru
- http://6x9elit.ru
- http://allbesttoys.ru
- http://archivespro.ru
- http://stom-mds.ru
- http://elite-book.ru
- http://foreland.ardmedia.ru
- http://twinside.ru
- http://nikolfleur.ru
- http://selena-beauty.ru
- http://tlgcom.ru
- http://pppe.ru
- http://tdpromhim.ru
- http://vip-divan.com
- http://sunshading.ru
- · ...and maintained many others

Github, developing, non-commercial

- http://snarksliveshere.xyz (Laravel. guest account: test/test)
- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/strela (Converted PSD to HTML/CSS/JS, don`t integration yet)

- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/vue.spa (test Vue page)
- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/csscleaner (for clean unused css)
- https://github.com/snarksliveshere/laravel-upload.local (Laravel CRM, developing)

ARD media websites

- stroy.ardmedia.ru
- http://stom1.ardmedia.ru
- http://stom2.ardmedia.ru
- http://salon1.ardmedia.ru
- http://salon2.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo6.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo7.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo8.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo12.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo13.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo14.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo15.ardmedia.ru
- http://demo16.ardmedia.ru

EDUCATION MS in Psychology

September 2000 - Aug 2005

GAUGN

https://gaugn.ru/en-us/

State Academic University for the Humanities

INTERESTS Right now my interests are php & modern frameworns. At this moment, I'm starting to

learn Symfony

LANGUAGES Russian fluent,

English mostly for reading technical documention, I'm a bit out of speaking practice

Mihail Deryugin 2